Pretty cool, huh? Probably would have
cost, like, 200 bucks in a store.
(Amy:)I do appreciate a bargain.
(Amy:)This entire ensemble
once belonged to my dead grandmother.
- You're kidding?
- Everything except bra and panties.
(Amy:)They're a leopard-spotted secret
I share with Victoria.
And now me, heh.
(Amy:)I just have one question
about the chair.
(Penny:)And what's that?
(Amy:)Aren't you worried about it
being unhygienic?
(Penny:)No. It's completely fi...
(Penny:)Hmm.
(Penny:)I get it. Sheldon sent you.
He put you up to this.
- No, he didn't.
- Really?
(Amy:)Yes, he did, he absolutely did.
Oh, my God, Amy,
that's really crappy of you.
- It is?
- Yeah.
(Penny:)Letting Sheldon use you
to manipulate me?
(Penny:)I thought you were my friend.
(Amy:)No, I am your friend.
Please don't be mad at me.